[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is Artificial Intelligence (AI)?",
    "answers": [
      " is a subset of machine learning that involves creating neural networks with multiple layers, which can learn and recognize patterns in large datasets.",
      " is a branch of computer science that focuses on creating machines that can perform tasks that normally require human intelligence.",
      "is a subset of AI that involves creating algorithms that can learn and improve from experience, without being explicitly programmed."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "is a branch of computer science that focuses on creating machines that can perform tasks that normally require human intelligence."
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is machine learning?",
    "answers": [
      "is a subset of AI that involves creating algorithms that can learn and improve from experience, without being explicitly programmed.",
      "is a subset of AI that involves creating algorithms that can learn and improve from experience, without being explicitly programmed."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "is a subset of AI that involves creating algorithms that can learn and improve from experience, without being explicitly programmed."
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Who are the pioneers of artificial intelligence?",
    "answers": [
      "Elon Musk and Steve Jobs",
      "John McCarthy and Marvin Lee Minsky",
      "Xavier Niel and Mounir Mahjoubi"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "John McCarthy and Marvin Lee Minsky"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What are concrete uses of AI?",
    "answers": [
      "To control the movements of individuals, direct air strikes, divert confidential data.",
      "To have groceries delivered, to render court decisions, for the electoral count.",
      "In telemedicine, autonomous driving, machine translation."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "In telemedicine, autonomous driving, machine translation."
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What would be one of the areas concerned by the future law of robotics?",
    "answers": [
      "The protection of privacy and intellectual property",
      "The fight against global warming",
      "Health and Sport Law"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Privacy and Intellectual Property"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "In what decade does artificial intelligence appear?",
    "answers": [" 1950", "1960", "1950"],
    "correctAnswer": " 1950"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "Question": "AI uses different sciences and knowledge. What are they?",
    "answers": [
      " Physics, chemistry, computer science, biology and mathematics.",
      " Computer science, electronics, mathematics, neuroscience and cognitive science.",
      "Social networks, computer science, digital sciences, philosophy, science and techniques of physical activities."
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Computer science, electronics, mathematics, neuroscience and cognitive science."
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is the term for the process of setting a price for a product or service?",
    "answers": ["Pricing", "Sales", "Social Listening", "Marketing Metrics"],
    "correctAnswer": "Pricing"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which country is the leading investor in AI?",
    "answers": ["China", "The France", "The United States"],
    "correctAnswer": " The United States "
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What do Asimov's laws say?",
    "answers": [
      "Economic principles concerning the data market",
      "Policy principles for data protection",
      "General ethical principles for the operation of robots"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "General ethical principles for the operation of robots"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What would be one of the areas concerned by the future law of robotics?",
    "answers": [
      "The Law of Health and Sport",
      "The fight against global warming",
      "Privacy and Intellectual Property"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Privacy and Intellectual Property"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What is the objective for the European Union in terms of AI? :",
    "answers": [
      "Becoming the world leader in AI",
      "Creating a European space and a single market for data",
      "Developing a data-driven economy without a legal framework in order to develop a dynamic and sustainable economy"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Creating a European space and a single market for data"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "An intelligent system is a computer system that mimics or acts in all circumstances with the decision-making capabilities of a",
    "answers": ["human expert", "Brand Identity"],
    "correctAnswer": "human expert"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Which approach is not artificial intelligence?",
    "answers": ["Act like humans", "Act intelligently", "Think like humans"],
    "correctAnswer": "Act smart"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What is the process of creating a message that resonates with a specific audience and motivates them to take action called?",
    "answers": ["Brand Identity", "Message Development"],
    "correctAnswer": "Message Development"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "Cognitive science is part of artificial intelligence?",
    "answers": ["false", "true"],
    "correctAnswer": " false "
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Does designing an agent that acts rationally mean that he?",
    "answers": ["Works autonomously", "memorizes perceived states"],
    "correctAnswer": " Works autonomously "
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What is the name of the workshop, organized in 1956, giving birth to AI?",
    "answers": ["Mac Carty's Workshop", "Dartmouth's Workshop"],
    "correctAnswer": " Dartmouth Workshop "
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Which discipline(s) are part of Artificial Intelligence?",
    "answers": ["Robotics", "Expert Systems"],
    "correctAnswer": "Robotics"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Humanoids are:?",
    "answers": ["Human-like robots", "Intelligent robots", "Human engineers"],
    "correctAnswer": "Human-like robots"
  }
]
